Guide to the Women's Basketball records, 1976-[ongoing]
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Women's Basketball records 1976-[ongoing]
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. Sports Information Office.
17.5 Linear Feet 17,500 Items
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches.
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the women's basketball team at Duke University. The material ranges in date from 1976-ongoing.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Women's Basketball records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the SI Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the women's basketball team at Duke University. There are also files regarding the Ronald McDonald House Challenge and the Dial Classic. The material ranges in date from 1976-ongoing.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Basketball for women -- North Carolina -- Durham -- History
Duke University. Sports Information Office
Duke University -- Sports
Related Material
Athletic Dept. Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletics Reference Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Chanticleer Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Non-Revenue Sports Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photographic Negative Collection
University Archives, Duke University.
Scrapbooks
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Yearly files, 1977-[ongoing], 21 Boxes
  The Yearly files contain clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, and programs about the baseball team at Duke University.
  - 1977-1982 (Box 1)
  - 1982-1986 (Box 2)
  - 1986-1988 (Box 3)
  - 1988-1991 (Box 4)
  - 1991-1993 (Box 5)
  - 1992/1993-1994/1995 (Box 6)
  - 1994/1995-1995/1996 (Box 7)
  - 1996/1997-1997/1998 (Box 8)
  - 1997/1998 (Box 9)
  - 1997/1998-1998/1999 (Box 10)
  - 1998/1999 (Box 11)
  - 1998/1999 (Box 12)
  - 1998/1999 (Box 13)
  - 1999/2000 (Box 14)
  - 1999/2000 (Box 15)
  - 2000/2001 (Box 16)
  - 2000/2001 (Box 17)
  - 2000/1001-2001/2002 (Box 18)
  - 2001/2002 (Box 19)
  - 2001/2002 (Box 20)
  - 2001/2002 (Box 21)
- Guides and Game Programs, 1976-[ongoing], 4 Boxes
  - 1976-1999 (Box 22)
  - 1998-2000 (Box 23)
  - 2000-2002 (Box 24)
  - 2001-2002, 2008/2009 (Box 25)